export const featuresAPI = [{"ipa":"ɒ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"+","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɑ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"+","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɶ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"+","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"a","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"+","front":"-","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ӕ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"+","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʌ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"ɔ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"o","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɤ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɘ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"œ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"ə","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"-","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"e","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɞ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"-","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"ø","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɛ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"ɵ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɯ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"u","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ʊ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"ɨ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ʉ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"y","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"i","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ʏ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"ɪ","syllabic":"+","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"-"},{"ipa":"ɫ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɴ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"-","delayed release":"0","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"+","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʀ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"+","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɲ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"-","delayed release":"0","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"+","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʎ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ŋ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"-","delayed release":"0","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"+","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʟ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"+","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɳ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"-","delayed release":"0","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"+","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʙ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"+","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɭ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɺ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"+","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɻ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɽ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"+","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"r","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"+","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"n","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"-","delayed release":"0","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"+","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"m","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"-","delayed release":"0","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"+","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"l","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɾ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"+","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɱ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"+","continuant":"-","delayed release":"0","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"+","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"+","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʔ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"+","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"k̟͡x̟","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɡ̟͡ɣ̟","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ħ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"+","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʕ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"+","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʁ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"q","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"χ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɢ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɕ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɟ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʝ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"c","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ç","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d͡ʑ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t͡ɕ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɣ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"x","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"k","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɡ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʑ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʈ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɖ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɬ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʐ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɸ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʂ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʒ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"z","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"v","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"+","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʃ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"s","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"p","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"f","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"+","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"b","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"θ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɮ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ð","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"β","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d͡ʒ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d͡z","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d͡ɮ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d̠͡ɮ̠","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t͡ʃ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t͡ɬ̲","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t͡s","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t͡ɬ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t̪͡s̪","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t̪͡ɬ̪","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d̪͡z̪","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d̪͡ɮ̪","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"+","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʈ͡ʂ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɖ͡ʐ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"p͡f","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"+","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"b͡v","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"+","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"p͡ɸ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"b͡β","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"t̪͡θ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"d̪͡ð","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"c͡ç","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɟ͡ʝ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"k͡x","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"k̠͡x̠","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɡ͡ɣ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɡ̠͡ɣ̠","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"q͡χ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɢ͡ʁ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"-","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɧ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"k͡p","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɡ͡b","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"p͡t","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"b͡d","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"+","sonorant":"-","continuant":"-","delayed release":"-","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"+","distributed":"-","strident":"+","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ɰ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɰ̠","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"w","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɥ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"j","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"+","back":"-","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɹ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"+","anterior":"-","distributed":"+","strident":"-","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʋ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"+","continuant":"+","delayed release":"0","approximant":"+","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"-","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"-","labiodental":"+","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"ʍ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"+","constr gl":"-","labial":"+","round":"+","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"+","high":"+","low":"-","front":"-","back":"+","tense":"+"},{"ipa":"ɦ","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"+","spread gl":"+","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"},{"ipa":"h","syllabic":"-","stress":"-","long":"-","consonantal":"-","sonorant":"-","continuant":"+","delayed release":"+","approximant":"-","tap":"-","trill":"-","nasal":"-","voice":"-","spread gl":"+","constr gl":"-","labial":"-","round":"-","labiodental":"-","coronal":"-","anterior":"0","distributed":"0","strident":"0","lateral":"-","dorsal":"-","high":"0","low":"0","front":"0","back":"0","tense":"0"}]